{
    "user_name": "lschuth",
    "session_complete_time": "2018-12-03 10:51:26.824339",
    "session_pk": 10,
    "session_size": 6,
    "block_size": 6,
    "policy_id": 1,
    "block_data": [
        {
            "block_id": 40,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 237,
                    "question_pk": 130,
                    "question": "I tried abseiling recently, as part of a family fun day.",
                    "chunk": "of a family fun day",
                    "chunk_translation": "eines Familienspa\u00dftages",
                    "answer": "of a family fun day",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 238,
                    "question_pk": 1091,
                    "question": "Days later, back home in California, I was purple from the waist down.",
                    "chunk": "Days later, back home in California",
                    "chunk_translation": "Tage sp\u00e4ter, zur\u00fcck in Kalifornien",
                    "answer": "Days later back home in California",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 239,
                    "question_pk": 471,
                    "question": "Sebastian began to cry: he could see I was in pain.",
                    "chunk": "he could see I was in pain",
                    "chunk_translation": "Er konnte sehen, dass ich Schmerzen hatte",
                    "answer": "He could see I was in pain",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 240,
                    "question_pk": 1202,
                    "question": "The first day I woke up after closing the loop, I was blown away by how much better I felt.",
                    "chunk": "how much better I felt",
                    "chunk_translation": "Wie viel besser f\u00fchlte ich mich",
                    "answer": "how much better I felt",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 241,
                    "question_pk": 345,
                    "question": "I was thinking of the summer I had planned with my sister, and my last thought was, That's a shame.",
                    "chunk": "had planned with my sister",
                    "chunk_translation": "hatte mit meiner Schwester geplant",
                    "answer": "had plans with my sister",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 242,
                    "question_pk": 1254,
                    "question": "The most important thing is that people don't have to wait.",
                    "chunk": "that people don't have to wait",
                    "chunk_translation": "dass die Leute nicht warten m\u00fcssen",
                    "answer": "that people don't have to wait",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 41,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 243,
                    "question_pk": 1199,
                    "question": "That's how we created what is in effect an artificial pancreas, or a closed loop system.",
                    "chunk": "a closed loop system",
                    "chunk_translation": "ein geschlossenes System",
                    "answer": "a loop closed system",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 244,
                    "question_pk": 704,
                    "question": "The boys said the movement was just the wind and wanted to keep going, but I went over and saw the head and hooves of a lamb coming out of her body.",
                    "chunk": "of a lamb coming out of her body",
                    "chunk_translation": "eines Lammes, das aus ihrem K\u00f6rper kommt",
                    "answer": "of a lamb coming out of her body",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 245,
                    "question_pk": 789,
                    "question": "I felt very attached to the brave pair and found it quite hard to leave them.",
                    "chunk": "to the brave pair ",
                    "chunk_translation": "zu dem tapferen Paar",
                    "answer": "to the brave pair",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 246,
                    "question_pk": 691,
                    "question": "We'd recently bought a house five minutes from the Downs, in Lewes, East Sussex, and headed towards Mount Caburn, the highest point in the area.",
                    "chunk": "the highest point in the area",
                    "chunk_translation": "der h\u00f6chste Punkt in der Gegend",
                    "answer": "the highest point in the area",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 247,
                    "question_pk": 679,
                    "question": "I also teach children and adults with learning difficulties, because I want to give others the chances I had.",
                    "chunk": "to give others the chances I had",
                    "chunk_translation": "um anderen die Chancen zu geben, die ich hatte",
                    "answer": "to give others the chances I had",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 248,
                    "question_pk": 1214,
                    "question": "We designed it for safety: if something breaks or I lose it, I can go back to using my insulin pump manually.",
                    "chunk": "go back to using my insulin pump manually",
                    "chunk_translation": "gehe zur\u00fcck, um meine Insulinpumpe manuell zu benutzen",
                    "answer": "go back to use my insulin pump manually",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 42,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 249,
                    "question_pk": 331,
                    "question": "Initially, the guys thought I'd skied on and would be waiting around the corner.",
                    "chunk": "waiting around the corner",
                    "chunk_translation": "Warte um die Ecke",
                    "answer": "waiting around the corner",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 250,
                    "question_pk": 756,
                    "question": "I felt joyous, but there was still more we had to do to make sure the lamb stayed alive.",
                    "chunk": "to make sure the lamb stayed alive",
                    "chunk_translation": "um sicherzustellen, dass das Lamm am Leben blieb",
                    "answer": "to make sure the lamb stayed alive",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 251,
                    "question_pk": 64,
                    "question": "I was 102 then, but thought, Why not?",
                    "chunk": "I was 102 then, but thought",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ich war damals 102, dachte aber",
                    "answer": "I was 102 then but thought",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 252,
                    "question_pk": 1094,
                    "question": "I was in an immobiliser for six weeks, to keep my leg straight, and it was three months before I could drive.",
                    "chunk": "keep my leg straight",
                    "chunk_translation": "halte mein Bein gerade",
                    "answer": "keep my leg straight",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 253,
                    "question_pk": 357,
                    "question": "It was really quite peaceful: I saw a forest either side of me, and I was just walking into it.",
                    "chunk": "was really quite peaceful",
                    "chunk_translation": "war wirklich sehr friedlich",
                    "answer": "was really quite peaceful",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 254,
                    "question_pk": 325,
                    "question": "It was horrible, lying there not being able to move, nobody knowing where I was or having any way of finding me.",
                    "chunk": "knowing where I was ",
                    "chunk_translation": "zu wissen, wo ich war",
                    "answer": "knew where I was",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 43,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 255,
                    "question_pk": 1232,
                    "question": "This is why we created OpenAPS  the Open Artificial Pancreas System project: to make the code, design and documentation available to others for free, so they can build a pancreas of their own.",
                    "chunk": "the code, design and documentation ",
                    "chunk_translation": "der Code, das Design und die Dokumentation",
                    "answer": "the code the design and the documentation",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 256,
                    "question_pk": 1122,
                    "question": "I was diagnosed with type 1 diabetes when I was 14.",
                    "chunk": "when I was 14",
                    "chunk_translation": "als ich 14 war",
                    "answer": "when I was 14",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 257,
                    "question_pk": 100,
                    "question": "I was married, for a very long time, to the best wife in the world and she died very suddenly of a stroke when she was 68.",
                    "chunk": "the best wife ",
                    "chunk_translation": "die beste Frau",
                    "answer": "the best wife",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 258,
                    "question_pk": 805,
                    "question": "I was the watch manager at a local station of the Berlin fire department that Friday, 15 December 2017.",
                    "chunk": "of the Berlin fire department ",
                    "chunk_translation": "von der Berliner Feuerwehr",
                    "answer": "of the Berlin Fire Department",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 259,
                    "question_pk": 705,
                    "question": "The boys said the movement was just the wind and wanted to keep going, but I went over and saw the head and hooves of a lamb coming out of her body.",
                    "chunk": "coming out of her body",
                    "chunk_translation": "aus ihrem K\u00f6rper kommen",
                    "answer": "coming out of her body",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 260,
                    "question_pk": 1204,
                    "question": "The first day I woke up after closing the loop, I was blown away by how much better I felt.",
                    "chunk": "The first day ",
                    "chunk_translation": "Der erste Tag",
                    "answer": "The first day",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 44,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 261,
                    "question_pk": 1024,
                    "question": "The handlebars of the zip line had caught in the V of a tree branch.",
                    "chunk": "the zip line ",
                    "chunk_translation": "die Zip-Linie",
                    "answer": "the zip line",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 262,
                    "question_pk": 19,
                    "question": "I was securely fastened in, so I knew I wouldn't fall out.",
                    "chunk": "I knew I wouldn't fall out",
                    "chunk_translation": "Ich wusste, dass ich nicht herausfallen w\u00fcrde",
                    "answer": "I knew I wouldn't fall out",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 263,
                    "question_pk": 866,
                    "question": "The unlocked safe had been there when they moved in and was in an area they didn't use much.",
                    "chunk": "when they moved in and was ",
                    "chunk_translation": "als sie eingezogen sind und war",
                    "answer": "when they were moved in and",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 264,
                    "question_pk": 1200,
                    "question": "The first day I woke up after closing the loop, I was blown away by how much better I felt.",
                    "chunk": "after closing the loop",
                    "chunk_translation": "nach dem Schlie\u00dfen der Schleife",
                    "answer": "after closing the loop",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 265,
                    "question_pk": 983,
                    "question": "Hopefully the boy will be more careful next time he plays hide and seek  but at least we know the combination to the safe now.",
                    "chunk": "we know the combination to the safe now",
                    "chunk_translation": "Wir kennen die Kombination jetzt zum Safe",
                    "answer": "we know the combination to the safe now",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 266,
                    "question_pk": 453,
                    "question": "There was traffic on the road and, although I was pretty out of it, I knew we weren't going to make it to the hospital.",
                    "chunk": "was pretty out of it",
                    "chunk_translation": "war ziemlich draus",
                    "answer": "was pretty out of it",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "block_id": 45,
            "qanda_data": [
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 267,
                    "question_pk": 1099,
                    "question": "I have to sleep with the TV on, as I can't bear the silence.",
                    "chunk": "can't bear the silence",
                    "chunk_translation": "kann die Stille nicht ertragen",
                    "answer": "can't bear the silence",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 268,
                    "question_pk": 1096,
                    "question": "I was in an immobiliser for six weeks, to keep my leg straight, and it was three months before I could drive.",
                    "chunk": "before I could drive",
                    "chunk_translation": "bevor ich fahren konnte",
                    "answer": "before I could drive",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 269,
                    "question_pk": 360,
                    "question": "No one had any avalanche gear  no transceivers to locate me, no probes and no shovels to dig me out  so the boys were just sticking their hands in the snow.",
                    "chunk": "to dig me out  ",
                    "chunk_translation": "um mich auszugraben",
                    "answer": "to dig me out",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 270,
                    "question_pk": 548,
                    "question": "Probably, but I do think that this way it's a nice story to remember.",
                    "chunk": "think that this way ",
                    "chunk_translation": "denke das so",
                    "answer": "think that this way",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 271,
                    "question_pk": 738,
                    "question": "There was a moment when I thought: I'm really going to put my hands inside a sheep.",
                    "chunk": "put my hands inside a sheep",
                    "chunk_translation": "leg meine H\u00e4nde in ein Schaf",
                    "answer": "put my hands inside a sheep",
                    "answer_correct": true,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                },
                {
                    "qanda_pk": 272,
                    "question_pk": 90,
                    "question": "That was an achievement  for me or my mother, I'm not sure.",
                    "chunk": "an achievement  for me or my mother",
                    "chunk_translation": "eine Leistung f\u00fcr mich oder meine Mutter",
                    "answer": "an achievement for me or my mother",
                    "answer_correct": false,
                    "qanda_type": "explore"
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}